I, high school detective, Kudō Shin'ichi...
...with Ran, my girlfriend since childhood, visited an amusement park.
However, I ended up witnessing a shady deal being done by men in black...
And I was drugged...
And thus I shrank.
If there was news that Kudō Shin'ichi is alive,
any harm may come to those around me.
Thus I became Edogawa Conan.
I'm trying to obtain intel about Black Organisation.
The ones who know my true identity are...
Dr. Agasa...
...and my classmate Haibara Ai.
Her true name is Miyano Shiho.
She was a member of the Black Organisation, codenamed Sherry.
The developer of the drug; APTX4869 which shrank my body.
Having her elder sister shot dead...
...and caught while trying to escape, took the drug willingly...
Sharnk and become Haibara Ai.
She's researching for an antidote.
What we know so far is that alcohol is one of the contents in APTX4869.
It can reverse the effect temporarily.
Even if I shrank, my intelligence is still the same!
The truth shall prevail!